[Episode 3]
Who is it?
Let me use the bathroom.
The bathroom... Let me use the bathroom!
This isn't the public restroom!
I'm going to pee my pants.
Let me use the bathroom.
Then go! I won't stop you.
What a psycho!
Hey, you!
Hey! Australia, right?
Right? Right? Australia, in Melbourne.
Don't you remember me?
No.
I'm pretty sure...
Do you live here?
Yes.
Maybe he's not the same person?
Is this your house?
No, it's not mine.
We just rent out the basement.
This house is a rich person's house, right?
Yes.
So...
Is it a really rich family's house?
But hey! Why would you pee on someone's house?
Why would you do that?
You peed here!
I marked this place as my territory. Why?
What?
Dogs mark their territory like this.
What the... Why would this be your territory?
See you again. I'll come to pee again tomorrow.
What's with him?
So is he saying that he's a dog? What?
That's right. I'm a dog.
Not a human being. A dog!
Your mom was a famous movie star a long time ago...
And your brother is one of
the top singers in our country.
Nice, huh?
We looked for the orphanage
you and your sister are from.
You two are twins.
What a psycho!
Eww! How disgusting.
How filthy!
A million dollars!
Are you Korean?
You're Korean?
I have a husband! And kids!
Just go to sleep. If you don't want to die.
[Start paying attenshun crazee brat]
Jason sent you here, didn't you?
Jason sent you here to kill me!
Did you think I'll get tricked?
Do you really think I was going
to get tricked by you, old man!
How can that lady be my mom?
She is your mother!
Don't lie!
If she's so great, why would she abandon me?
With that money, she can buy all the milk
in the world and raise 1,000 children!
It's not like life was hard on her,
or that she's starving.
How? Not one but two? How could she?
Your mom is that kind of lady.
Anything that gets in her way, she'll throw away!
She's capable of that. Your mom does what she wants.
Shut your mouth. I'm going to kill you.
I'm going to kill you, old man!
Grandpa, I want to die!
Why, did your mom cause an accident again?
I don't want her as my mom! I want to die!
Why? What'd she do this time?
She's not my mom!
I can't live with her!
Did he come looking for me? All the way from Australia?
But how'd he know where I live?
Is he a psycho?
Hey, Yun.
Pork?
I'm going to put it in the sauce for noodles.
It's not in your fridge? Would you buy some?
The side meat.
Okay. Thanks.
I'm an excellent cook.
Fried pork. Braised beef. Noodles. Pasta.
I also clean, wash dishes,
and do laundry extremely well.
There's nothing I can't do well, to be honest.
Later, I probably can raise babies well.
You won't have to lift a finger.
I guess we'll just have to wait and see.
But I think I'd make an excellent husband.
Do you like me that much?
Do rabbits like carrots?
You're in big trouble, Choi Yun.
You have such poor taste in women.
Don't make me sad anymore.
Make me sad again, and I'll really die then.
[I'll wait by your house. I'll wait till you get home
- From: Your Yeongwoo]
Sorry.
Pork.
Did he tell me to buy the front leg? Or back leg?
Or was it the side?
I'm such a blockhead.
I should just die!
You know how much I worked
to get that shirt? Give it back...
Brats like this should rot in jail!
She doesn't know any better.
Let it go, why don't you?
Why make a big deal over stealing just one shirt?
Just one shirt?
With just this one shirt, I can feed my whole family!
It's hard enough as is these days!
Why did you steal it?
Didn't Galchi teach you that it's bad to steal clothes?
- I gave money.
- You did?
Sure, you paid! You only gave me a dollar
and it costs $28!
She wasn't really stealing then.
What? Do you like her or something?
All the guys are after her in this area!
If you don't put her in jail today, you'll be sorry!
What are you crying for?
Ma'am. Calm down!
Huh, what are you crying for?
Ma'am! Calm down!
Please, sit down, ma'am!
Let's talk about this.
Do not judge. Lead him down the righteous path.
Lead him, I pray, not in the path of ease and comfort,
but under the stress and spur
of difficulties and challenge.
Here let him learn to stand up in the storm,
here let him learn compassion for those who fail.
Then I, his father, will dare to whisper
"I have not lived in vain."
That was Audrey, reciting MacArthur's "Build Me a Son."
The song playing is "For The One"
by Korea's top singer, Choi Yun.
Choi Yun is Audrey's son.
And we'll finish up with this song.
Great job today.
You should have your own show!
- Oh, you're too kind!
- Right?
I should tell my boss to give you a show!
If I ask you to do a show,
you are not allowed to say no.
That's just too much. Stop it.
Thank you so much. The next recording is at 2 p.m.
I'll see you later. Goodbye.
Excuse me. Let's talk for a minute.
Yes?
A couple days ago, there was a morning
special adoption show, right?
- Yes, there was.
- There was a guy on it who...
Oh, they must be twins!
How cute.
Sorry, l will contact you later.
Oh? Okay. Thank you. Goodbye.
I'm sorry, but can I hold your baby?
How adorable!
May I feed him?
Want some milk?
You don't want it? He doesn't want any.
Here you go. Your twins are too cute.
I want to raise twins, too.
Your mother must feel so happy!
It hurts...
Gently!
Wake up!
The sun is up, you guys!
Hanchae!
Eww! You all disgust me.
If only I could put you back into my stomach!
Sukchae, wake up. Wake up!
Get up!
Eunchae! Wake up!
Where's Eunchae?
Would she fit beneath the bed, Mom?
She's probably bailing Yun
out of something crazy he did.
He's not causing trouble, he's a genius.
You're so stupid!
Why you little...
You'd hit your own mother?
That's what I'm saying!
Sorry! Sorry, Mom!
That really hurt!
I think that girl with the thick lips recognizes you.
She probably thinks I just look familiar.
Eat. Hard boiled eggs in saunas are the best!
You should have gone somewhere else! Why here?
If we're caught, we're dead!
Just eat it.
You found us!
So this is what a sauna looks like.
Right?
- It's fun.
- Told you.
Hey, not you, too!
What will you do if another scandal breaks loose?
I got it. I'll be careful.
I don't have makeup on. They won't recognize me.
- Fruit ice cream is killer here.
- Yeah. We should come here all the time.
Yeah, it is him.
Isn't that Choi Yun?
- Where?
- Really?
- It is him!
- Choi Yun!
What should we do?
What do we do, Eunchae?
I'll cause a distraction. You guys sneak out, okay?
Why are you crying?
Ma'am! What am I going to do?
What's the matter?
Did someone hit you?
No...
My butt was burning...
What?
The sauna's really hot, ma'am.
How embarrassing!
How embarrassing.
Yun. Where are you?
Olympic Parkway.
Olympic Parkway?
I'm going to drive Minju home and come home.
Hey, you're bleeding! Does it sting? It stings, huh?
Why weren't you more careful?
Oh, Minju fell and scratched her knee.
You should have been more careful.
It's okay. I can take the bus.
Okay.
Mother.
You look normal, but how sad.
Here.
Thank you.
Let's go, Mother. She at least looks normal.
Her parents must be so disappointed.
Sorry.
Did you eat?
You didn't eat, did you?
You don't look like you did.
You like me that much?
What's so great about me that you'd
come all the way here from Australia?
Do you know anyone in Korea?
You don't even know anyone here,
and yet you still came for me?
We didn't even get to talk that much.
And I'm not someone men fall for at first sight.
In any case, thank you...
For liking a girl like me.
I don't have much to offer, but do you
want to have dinner at my place?
Let's go.
I can't give you my heart, but I can give you food.
Sorry...
Let's go.
This is Yun's house and our house is over here.
but my house is this way...
Hey, not there!
This isn't our house...
We have to get out!
We'll be in trouble if she comes home!
We have to leave!
We'll get in so much trouble.
Come on...
She probably had her reasons.
No one would ditch their child like that.
Stuff happens.
Maybe she was too poor to even feed me milk
and gave me up so I could have a better life.
Got the same eyes as your mother's.
Truth will prevail in the end.
The ancient scholars were very brilliant
to create such words of wisdom.
I'll make a lot of money and go back to Korea.
I'll meet my poor mother one day.
I'll buy her some pretty clothes,
some BBQ meat, and a beautiful house.
Mom, I'll go there and let you live in luxury.
Just wait five years!
[Goodbye, my love]
Oh, how sad...
Ma'am!
Oh, Eunchae, you're here?
Are you crying?
Stella is so tragic.
Stella?
Stella from "The Last Concert."
You've never watched "The Last Concert"?
No.
Stella is a sad girl who comes out in the movie,
She has leukemia and
later dies as she watches her lover's concert.
Oh...
How can her life be so tragic? Her mother dies...
Her father has an affair and flees with his lover...
And then to abandon Richard, who she loved.
How hard it must have been to die and leave him...
Take it easy, ma'am. It's just a movie.
It's just a movie, but my heart aches so badly!
I've watched it five times,
and every time my heart hurts.
Son, my son!
Don't you want to cheer me up? Go shopping with me.
It's not Yun...
Who is that man?
He's... Someone I sort of know.
He came into the wrong house. I'm sorry, ma'am.
What's with him?
Hey!
Why is that man crying?
I did something wrong. He must be hurt because of me.
But why did he look at me that way?
Mister.
Mister!
I'm sorry!
I'm flattered, but I already have someone I like...
There's no room for you...
I'm sorry!
Eat rice!
Hey, Galchi, eat.
I told you! I'm not going to talk to you anymore!
I'm sorry... I said sorry.
Talk to me, please?
Running around and stealing stuff...
I'm embarrassed to death because of you.
What a pain!
I won't do it again.
I won't.
You always say that!
Are you stupid, mom?
Didn't you know your mom was stupid?
If she doesn't know, you can just keep telling her.
You can teach her, you brat!
You think you know everything.
You better eat, now!
You know I'm a gangster, right?
Do you want to get hit or do you want to eat?
I said eat!
Drink water...
Drink it!
Even though your mom lives her life like that,
even though she's an idiot, she didn't leave you.
Hello?
It's me. Danny.
Muhyeok.
How are you?
Is Korea good?
Yeah, thanks to you. I checked into
a really nice hotel with the money you gave me.
You were right. It's a lot of money.
Enough to last me a lifetime. Thank you.
Why aren't you speaking in Korean?
Is there something wrong?
I called because I wanted to ask you something.
How long did the doctors say I have to live?
I heard I was dying, but I didn't find out
how much time I have left.
Muhyeok.
Do I have at least...
A year?
Not even...
Son, my son!
Don't you want to cheer me up?
Who is that man?
[Choi Yun's Midnight Concert]
Let's take ten!
It's your first time seeing me dance, huh?
How was it? The director says it's corny.
It was.
Really? You think it's corny, too?
Yes.
- It's corny?
- Huh?
I'm not doing the show. I'm going home.
Hey, what's wrong?
Is it really corny?
- Did I say that?
- Yes.
- When?
- Right now!
No. It was amazing.
So killer!
You definitely said it was corny.
I didn't!
Is it really killer!
Yes.
When other people say something,
you act as if nothing happened
but when I say something...
You act like it's the end of the world.
Of course! You always give me a hard time.
Am I your pet? Your toy?
No. A goddess.
You're my goddess. Did you not know that?
If you like it, it's good no matter what.
If you don't like it, it's the end of my world.
It was killer, right?
Yeah.
What are you doing here?
I have a shoot close to here.
I heard Yun singing. I'm taking a small break.
I missed him.
You should have called.
Where are you shooting?
Nearby. When are you singing?
In a little while.
When I think of my mother,
I'm grateful and I start to cry.
For giving birth to me and raising me so well.
Moving me with her endless love.
Mom, you are my sunshine. My world.
I love you, mom. I love you.
Why are you here?
To see Yun.
Let's go.
But there's still time until the shooting.
Let go.
Why are you doing this? Stop it!
Stop right there, Jo Yeongwoo!
Let go of her hand.
Go back and do your little dance.
You better let go!
Minju's my girl. Let go of her hand.
You starting a fight?
I told you to let go.
Fine. Let's end it today.
Say it now. Me or Choi Yun?
Me or Choi Yun?
Can you both let go of my wrists?
We're going to be on the front page
of the news tomorrow.
My dad is going to explode again.
Didn't you break up with him?
I did.
Kang Minju!
I did, but I don't think he can.
Do you want to see me die today?
Are you two competing?
Always saying you're going to die.
It's getting so old.
You guys will die over a woman?
You guys will die over love?
This is exhausting.
I should stop playing with kids.
- Minju!
- Minju.
I'm sorry, but I don't believe in love.
And guys like you who always talk about love
I especially don't believe.
Minju!
Yeongwoo, you said that if I died,
you'd die along with me.
Choi Yun, didn't you say you
loved me more than yourself?
Is that really true?
Could it be the truth?
Could a love like that really exist?
Minju!
Yun!
Save him!
Minju and Yun can't swim!
Neither can swim!
How is Minju?
Don't worry. She's fine.
Yun. Yun!
Stay still!
Would you like to wait a bit?
I'll bring Yun's clothes. Want to wear those?
Mister!
Wait!
You'll catch a cold like that. You'll freeze to death!
You really don't listen, do you?
Mister! Wake up!
Mister! Mister, wake up!
What'd you do all these years?
Not knowing how to swim.
It seems like you like that girl.
You must have been embarrassed a bit.
Are you the person who saved us?
Maybe...
Thanks, bro.
You don't have a brother, right?
Nope.
Want me to be your brother?
Want to be my little brother?
We'll see.
Don't want to?
Then don't!
Sure.
I'll be your little bro.
[Episode 4 Preview]
He seems totally into me.
Eunchae said she slept with a guy.
No, it's not what you think!
Now I'm seeing things.
[Sorry, I want to be by your side]
Don't be shy.
This is what you do when you're dating.
Are you being shy again?
[I wanted to call out Love's name just once]
Son!
Yun is sleeping.
Where's the medicine?